Emmanuel!
(God With Us – Matthew 1:23)
Good morning.
My name is Amanda, I came from the USA.
I just want to explain how I was born again through Emmanuel TV and Prophet T.B. Joshua.
It all started when I was really young.
I loved Jesus, I knew Jesus when I was a really young kid.
Then, as I got older, around 14, I started having problems in my life, and I started to doubt God,
I started to think that; "How could there be a God, if all these bad things can happen to me?"
So, I sort of denounced Jesus as a young child.
Right after that my problems got worse.
I started cutting myself with razors, doing drugs, drinking alcohol, rebelling against my parents.
I just went insane, I was put in mental hospitals all the time.
In the course of that I became suicidal and I tried to commit suicide all the time.
Even the doctors would say...
They would take my blood after I had taken so many drugs in an attempted suicide
and they would say, "I don't know how you are alive, but you are alive".
I would just say that I will just try again tomorrow; I was persistent.
I was always afraid of shooting myself with a gun, because I wanted to go in a much calmer way.
I also started dealing drugs in the US, like marijuana.
When I was doing that, along the lines, one day a voice spoke to me and said
that I would get robbed in this car with these people.
I didn't understand because this voice speaking to my heart, it felt like God.
I was like, "I don't believe in God, so how could this be?" but it turned out that I did get robbed.
I went to a friend's house and I knocked on the door.
I was like, "If my friend doesn't answer the door, I'm going to jump in front of a car and kill myself".
But she answered the door and I got home safely.
I wasn't ready to give my life to God, or to believe in God, or to know God was real;
I was too busy doing wordly things, so I put it away in my memories,
I locked it away for another time.
Then, I got even worse.
I started to actually think about committing suicide with a gun.
I remember what happened with the gun, and how a voice spoke to me that might have been God.
I started to question, "If I died, where would I was going to go?
Am I going to go to some place like 'no place' or am I going to a place worse than this?"
So, I just needed to know before I did this act, "Is He real?"
So, I started seeking on the internet; because when I was younger I experienced demonic attacks.
It's funny because when I denounced Jesus, the attacks stopped.
They would attack me at night; they would scare me, and they stopped when I denounced Jesus.
But I did know that demons were real.
I went on the internet because I used to play with a satanic things like ouija boards...
How did you discover Emmanuel TV that led to your deliverance?
When I was on YouTube, looking to see...
I wanted to hear demons say that God was real, because even the Bible says that
demons acknowledge the existence of God.
The very next thing that came up on Youtube was "Deliverances through Emmanuel TV".
I was intrigued by it.
But I always thought, "Maybe this could be fake. Maybe it is not real -
the healing, the deliverances, the testimonies - it could have all been faked".
But I kept watching; I ate, slept and breathed this Emmanuel TV, trying to figure it out.
I saw the good deeds that Prophet T.B. Joshua was doing.
The love that I saw out of this church - through all my life I've never really seen real love,
only the love that is temporary or selfish.
I just started to want to be a part of this, and a part of God.
What really touched me was the Word of God that Prophet T.B. Joshua teaches -
the Words of love and hope and who Jesus is.
Through that I began to change and I started listening and even praying.
At some point along the way, I found myself in my bathroom, thinking,
"God, I really want to be a part of this".
I was just speaking to Jesus, not in a church but in my bathroom,
"I don't know if You can hear me, I don't know if You are real, but these people seem happy,
I want to be a part of this."
I told it myself.
I was speaking to Him saying, "I'm a bad person; I lie, I steal, I cheat - I'm terrible."
I was like, "God, I'm just going to fix myself and then I'll come to You."
But then, at that moment, Jesus spoke to me, and He said to me,
"No, I will make you perfect" - because it is His work, not mine.
Shall we put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
When you started watching Emmanuel TV, your life started changing.
For the first time you believed God.
- Right?
- Yes!
Shall we put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
My advice for people is, "If you are going through a hard time in life, and you started to doubt God,
I just want people to know that living life without God is not easier, and He is not your enemy.
He loves you, He wants good things for you. Jesus loves you."
That is the most important thing I want people to know;
it is so much harder in life to be without knowing that love of God.
Hallelujah! Put your hands together for Jesus Christ!
You mean, you are totally delivered, no more suicidal thoughts,
and all those demonic spirits that caused you unbelief and all that?
Yes, when that happened, I felt the spiritual heaviness that was causing all of that,
to be pushed down into my feet, and I was free to praise God.
My heart was free; I have never felt so light in all my life.
From the morning that I woke up, I knew that God was real because He set me free.
It's amazing!
Let's put our hands together for Jesus one more time!
These are the cuts, scars on my legs from when I used to cut myself and do drugs,
like I have some on my arm.
Basically, that's what I would do and that was terrible - I would bleed for days and days.
I would keep doing it; I would cut myself hundreds of times a day - I liked it.
It was strange.
All these are over now?
Yes, I do not do that.
Let's clap for Jesus Christ!
To God be the glory.
We thank God Almighty for your life, for this wonderful deliverance you have received
through watching Emmanuel TV, listening to the message of Prophet T.B. Joshua.
Now, that the Lord Almighty has set you free;
the Bible says those who are delivered by Christ's Word must be ruled by His Word.
We pray that God Almighty will give you the inner grace to make His Word the standard for your life,
so that your deliverance will be permanent.
TT ROBERT BEGIER 09/01/2019
RV: Mel Flowers 12/01/2019